<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>career on Tech stuff</title>
    <link>https://ptqa.github.io/tags/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in career on Tech stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 16:43:49 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ptqa.github.io/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Always ask for more</title>
      <link>https://ptqa.github.io/always_ask4more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 16:43:49 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptqa.github.io/always_ask4more/</guid>
      <description>Tech bubble Currently we&amp;rsquo;re living in a growing tech bubble. Rich people invest billions into tech companies that report huge losses. They expect that any of those companies can become next FAANG company. This brings a lot of money into tech industry, which drives compensation up. It&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon to see people reporting compensations up to 1 mln on blind. And if you don&amp;rsquo;t have 1kk compensation package - always ask for more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About certification</title>
      <link>https://ptqa.github.io/certifcation_aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 12:12:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptqa.github.io/certifcation_aws/</guid>
      <description>AWS certification Nowadays it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of sense to pay &amp;amp; prepare for various certification if you aim to improve your skills and increase your market value. Position require certification are rare and nobody will give you additional credit for being certified during interview. Especially it&amp;rsquo;s true if you origin from developing country. In example, in India various cases of fraud with certification were reported and I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about memorising dump files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start</title>
      <link>https://ptqa.github.io/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptqa.github.io/start/</guid>
      <description>Today I quit my current job (yet again). But no, I&amp;rsquo;m not joining another company straight away. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to take some time off and chill a bit. Not sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll have motivation to fill this blog with content, but I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best. 1 article per year maybe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>