<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tech stuff</title>
    <link>https://ptqa.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tech stuff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 01:58:54 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ptqa.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My cloud gaming setup</title>
      <link>https://ptqa.github.io/cloud_gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 01:58:54 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptqa.github.io/cloud_gaming/</guid>
      <description>I used to own Xbox One with Kinect around 5 years ago and had a lot of fun with it. My favorite games back then were Assassins Creed series, Prototype and Dishonored. At first I was thinking what should I buy PS4 or new Xbox? Maybe wait for next generation or fuck it and buy a gaming PC? But all of a sudden I found this &amp;lsquo;cloud gaming&amp;rsquo; thing. I was sceptical at first because milliseconds of latency matter in video games and I get around 40-50 ms to nearest AWS region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The mystery of docker &amp; .pyc</title>
      <link>https://ptqa.github.io/pyc_docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 04:05:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptqa.github.io/pyc_docker/</guid>
      <description>Docker containers are the same, right? Once upon a time developers showed me strange problem. There were trying to obfuscate python code by compiling .py files (python code) to .pyc files (python compiled bytecode) the problem was that client could not run this .pyc files although it worked on dev host (work on my machine). Turns out that devs were trying to run .pyc file like this:
$ chmod +x /app/run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start</title>
      <link>https://ptqa.github.io/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptqa.github.io/start/</guid>
      <description>Today I quit my current job (yet again). But no, I&amp;rsquo;m not joining another company straight away. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to take some time off and chill a bit. Not sure if I&amp;rsquo;ll have motivation to fill this blog with content, but I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best. 1 article per year maybe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>